[
  {
    "front": "porter à la main, posséder, avoir",
    "back": "持"
  },
  {
    "front": "connaître, savoir",
    "back": "知"
  },
  {
    "front": "enseigner",
    "back": "教"
  },
  {
    "front": "apprendre",
    "back": "習"
  },
  {
    "front": "finir, se terminer",
    "back": "終"
  },
  {
    "front": "papier",
    "back": "紙"
  },
  {
    "front": "terre, terrain, sol",
    "back": "地"
  },
  {
    "front": "plan, schéma, dessin",
    "back": "図"
  },
  {
    "front": "salle, pièce",
    "back": "室"
  },
  {
    "front": "origine, source",
    "back": "元"
  }
]
